http://www.avisca.com/terms_privacy.asp

Blog
Welcome to Avisca.com, your online store for African American Art prints and original Black art.Our updated site features a large selection of limited edition and open edition prints and posters by popular African American and Caribbean artists, with an expanded collection of abstract and decorative prints – all at everyday discounted prices.
Artist
Title
Subject
Limited Editions
Mini Prints
New Releases
Top Sellers
Decorative Art
Woman
Sign up for Avisca.com updates:
Follow Us :
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYProtecting your privacy is important to Avisca.com. We promise to keep your personal information confidential. The following statement describes how we gather and use personal information about you.Why we collect personal informationAvisca.com collects personal information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide (your name, email address, phone number, mailing address, credit card information) to process orders. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on new items, announcements, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. You may opt-out of receiving future communications at any time by emailing us at contact@avisca.com.Avisca.com will not rent, sell, nor share your name, address, email address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission.How we collect personal informationWe collect information about you in a few ways. When you purchase from us, give us your contact information when you correspond with us, request to join our mailing list, or register for any contests or promotions, we store the information you provide in our secure database.Like many web sites, we use "cookie" technology to make web shopping easier for you. "Cookies" enable us to track items placed in your shopping cart, and to identify you when you visit again.Avisca.com's web site contains links to other sites. Avisca.com does not share your personal information with those web sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices.
CUSTOMER SERVICE
Help
Shipping & Deliveries
Returns & Exchanges
SITE MAPS
Product Index
Category Index
MY ACCOUNT
Copyright ©  Avisca.com. All Rights Reserved.Built with Volusion
